https://www.dyslexia.uk.net/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
The Dyslexia Association is a registered charity that provides support and services for dyslexic children and adults of all ages, their parents/families, educators, employers and the wider community.
This privacy policy explains how we use any personal information that we collect when you contact us or use our services.
By providing us with your personal information, you accept and consent to the practices described in this policy.
For the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), the data controller is The Dyslexia Association and the Data Protection Officer is Julia McMurray (Senior Administrator)
What information do we collect about you?
We collect personal information about you when you contact us requesting support or services, for example via our Helpline or by booking an assessment.Â  We also collect information from feedback provided by you following the delivery of a service.Â  All of the information that we collect is held securely on our Customer Relationship Management (CRM) system and servers.
Personal information is any information that can be used to identify you.Â  The personal information we collect may include:
your name
name of your child (if they are the person who will receive the service)
address
date of birth
e-mail address
telephone number
employer name & address
educational establishment name & address
details of previous assessments or testing
medical conditions or medication which may affect any testing
How will we use the information about you?
We may use your information to:
provide services
send you communications requesting feedback on any service you have received
process job applications
Who has access to your information?
TDA staff and Associates have access to your personal information in the interests of delivering services to you.
We will not sell or rent your information to third-parties and we will not share your information for marketing purposes.
We use third-party service providers or organisations for the following purposes:
Survey Monkey – for the collection of feedback and questionnaires prior to assessments
WorldPay – for credit / debit card payments
GL Assessment – for children’s screenings
Dyscalculia Screener – for adult dyscalculia screenings
MailChimp – for our opt-in mailing list
JotForm – for job applications
Eventbrite – for booking events
We will not contact you for marketing purposes by e-mail, phone or text message unless you have given your prior consent by signing up to our mailing list.Â  We do not use postal marketing.
Your Rights
You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you.Â  If you would like a copy of some or all of the personal information we hold about you, please send a written request (e-mail or by post) to julia.mcmurray@dyslexia.uk.net
We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date.Â  You have the right to ask us to:
correct information you think is inaccurate
remove information you think is inaccurate
delete the records we hold on you
complain about the way your data is processed by us
If you would like to make any corrections, ask us to delete your information or complain about how we process your personal data, please contact Â julia.mcmurray@dyslexia.uk.net
Updated April 2018
Useful links
Confidentiality
Safeguarding
Donate
Online donation
Call us on 0115 924 6888
2020 © The Dyslexia Association. All rights reserved
